[
  {
    "surveyId": "61ebf7b30c9988bbea15462c",
    "userId": "9cddf165683c83093cf1",
    "responses": [
      {
        "questionId": "61ec0381929662b29c458d81",
        "questionText": "What generations of Pokemon have you played?",
        "questionType": "CHECKBOX",
        "value": {
          "response": [
            {
              "id": "c48ba5",
              "value": "Gen 3: Ruby, Sapphire, Emerald"
            },
            {
              "id": "7d004f",
              "value": "Gen 4: Diamond, Pearl, Platinum"
            }
          ]
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "surveyId": "61ebf7b30c9988bbea15462c",
    "userId": "39e872d8b9b8097ce818",
    "responses": [
      {
        "questionId": "61ec0381929662b29c458d81",
        "questionText": "What generations of Pokemon have you played?",
        "questionType": "CHECKBOX",
        "value": {
          "response": [
            {
              "id": "bfee3d",
              "value": "Gen 1: Red, Green, Blue, Yellow"
            },
            {
              "id": "052bb3",
              "value": "Gen 2: Gold, Silver, Crystal"
            },
            {
              "id": "c48ba5",
              "value": "Gen 3: Ruby, Sapphire, Emerald"
            },
            {
              "id": "7d004f",
              "value": "Gen 4: Diamond, Pearl, Platinum"
            },
            {
              "id": "80fc6e",
              "value": "Gen 5: White, Black, White 2, Black 2"
            },
            {
              "id": "d1a1b2",
              "value": "Gen 6: X, Y"
            },
            {
              "id": "27efe5",
              "value": "Gen 7: Sun, Moon, Ultra Sun, Ultra Moon"
            },
            {
              "id": "6c0115",
              "value": "Gen 8: Sword, Shield"
            }
          ]
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "surveyId": "61ebf7b30c9988bbea15462c",
    "userId": "9cddf165683c83093cf1",
    "responses": [
      {
        "questionId": "61ec0381929662b29c458d81",
        "questionText": "What generations of Pokemon have you played?",
        "questionType": "CHECKBOX",
        "value": {
          "response": [
            {
              "id": "052bb3",
              "value": "Gen 2: Gold, Silver, Crystal"
            },
            {
              "id": "c48ba5",
              "value": "Gen 3: Ruby, Sapphire, Emerald"
            },
            {
              "id": "7d004f",
              "value": "Gen 4: Diamond, Pearl, Platinum"
            },
            {
              "id": "80fc6e",
              "value": "Gen 5: White, Black, White 2, Black 2"
            },
            {
              "id": "d1a1b2",
              "value": "Gen 6: X, Y"
            },
            {
              "id": "27efe5",
              "value": "Gen 7: Sun, Moon, Ultra Sun, Ultra Moon"
            }
          ]
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "surveyId": "61ebf7b30c9988bbea15462e",
    "userId": "9cddf165683c83093cf1",
    "responses": [
      {
        "questionId": "61ef09228de613306d6bcc67",
        "questionText": "What is your name?",
        "questionType": "SHORT_ANSWER",
        "value": {
          "response": "Larry Bayou"
        }
      },
      {
        "questionId": "61ef09228de613306d6bcc68",
        "questionText": "What is your college affiliation?",
        "questionType": "SHORT_ANSWER",
        "value": {
          "response": "Oakes"
        }
      },
      {
        "questionId": "61ef09228de613306d6bcc69",
        "questionText": "If you have a favorite food, what is it?",
        "questionType": "SHORT_ANSWER",
        "value": {
          "response": "Fries"
        }
      },
      {
        "questionId": "61ef09228de613306d6bcc69",
        "questionText": "What city in Santa Cruz County do you live in?",
        "questionType": "MULT_CHOICE",
        "value": {
          "response": {
            "id": "ad4da4",
            "value": "Santa Cruz"
          }
        }
      },
      {
        "questionId": "61ef09228de613306d6bcc6b",
        "questionText": "Do you like to eat candy?",
        "questionType": "MULT_CHOICE",
        "value": {
          "response": {
            "id": "7ec6b6",
            "value": "No"
          }
        }
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "surveyId": "61ebf7b30c9988bbea15462e",
    "userId": "9cddf165683c83093cf1",
    "responses": [
      {
        "questionId": "61ef09228de613306d6bcc67",
        "questionText": "What is your name?",
        "questionType": "SHORT_ANSWER",
        "value": {
          "response": "Brandon Victoriano"
        }
      },
      {
        "questionId": "61ef09228de613306d6bcc68",
        "questionText": "What is your college affiliation?",
        "questionType": "SHORT_ANSWER",
        "value": {
          "response": "Kresge"
        }
      },
      {
        "questionId": "61ef09228de613306d6bcc69",
        "questionText": "If you have a favorite food, what is it?",
        "questionType": "SHORT_ANSWER",
        "value": {
          "response": "Poke"
        }
      },
      {
        "questionId": "61ef09228de613306d6bcc69",
        "questionText": "What city in Santa Cruz County do you live in?",
        "questionType": "MULT_CHOICE",
        "value": {
          "response": {
            "id": "ad4da4",
            "value": "Santa Cruz"
          }
        }
      },
      {
        "questionId": "61ef09228de613306d6bcc6b",
        "questionText": "Do you like to eat candy?",
        "questionType": "MULT_CHOICE",
        "value": {
          "response": {
            "id": "7ec6b6",
            "value": "Yes"
          }
        }
      }
    ]
  }
]
